A lot of stuff going on on this
September 11th Rashashana Feast of
Trumpets weekend and we're going to try
to cover everything that's going on. My
name is Tom. You are watching the
Watching River channel. I'm really glad
you're here. I hope you're well. Again,
today is September 11th, 2026
and uh beautiful day here by the river
in the middle of Connecticut. As far as
a live studio audience goes, crickets,
and I don't mean crickets have shown up.
Not even the cricket showed up, but
there's nothing here today. I don't see
any birds. I don't see any squirrels.
But if that changes, I'll let you know.
Okay, before we get into the seriousness
of our chat today, I think it's
important always to start off with the
word of God. I'm going to read the 23rd
Psalm today. The Lord is my shepherd. I
shall not want. He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures. He leadeth me beside
the still waters. He restoreth my soul.
He leadth me in the paths of
righteousness for his name's sake. Yay,
though I walk through the valley of the
shadow of death, I will fear no evil.
For thou art with me. Thy rod and thy
staff, they comfort me. Thou preparest a
table before me in the presence of mine
enemies. Thou anointest my head with
oil. My cup runth over. Surely goodness
and mercy shall follow me all the days
of my life, and I will dwell in the
house of the Lord forever. Give me an
amen.
Thank you. I heard that. So, I guess we
should probably start off here. Um,
it is the 25th anniversary of the 9/11
attacks.
And actually last night in New York
City, they had a drone display that used
2,977
drones and it recreated the Twin Towers
and each one of those drones was
representing a life lost on 911. I think
most of us who are old enough to
remember exactly where we were and what
we were doing 25 years ago this morning.
I remember just looking at a computer
screen to get ready for my day in my
home office and I saw a thumbnail
picture on a news site that showed one
of the World Trade Center towers on fire
and I thought that's not funny. That was
the I thought thought it was almost like
a meme or something and I clicked on it
and it said that a plane had flown into
the first tower and I just ran
immediately downstairs because I was
living in a two family house and I went
to talk to the people downstairs and
said to them, "Turn on the TV. Turn on
the TV right now." And I mean the moment
they turned on the TV, the newscaster
said the second tower was just struck.
And we didn't know what was going on.
anyone everyone has the memory of where
they were that day, but we had no clue
if we were truly under attack or what
was going on. And uh 25 years later, we
still don't know really exactly what
happened. I don't think maybe we do.
Some are sure they do, some are not
sure, but I know one thing. Everything
turned a corner that day. And I remember
saying to those people that day who were
believers,
we're in the last days. This was 25
years ago. I'm like, we just turned a
major corner. And you know what? Anyone
who's old enough to remember what life
was like before 9/11 and life was like
in this country after 911, there were
major changes, you know, major changes.
Remember walking into an airport and you
could go all the way. There was no
security, you know. I think there might
have been a metal detector. I don't even
know if there was that, but we just walk
right up to where the flights were. We'd
hug our loved ones. we'd see them off
and you know and everything changed in
every way after u 9/11 you know but we
do remember the families and the victims
of that day 25 years can you believe
it's been 25 years and who knew when
that happened that 25 years later to the
day the feast of trumpets would be on
that day you wonder you just wonder
could it have been some kind of 25-year
warning to the United States I don't
know God knows I don't
But we're living in a fascinating
weekend this weekend between Feast of
Trumpets and remembering 9/11 and
they've got a bricks conference and
other things are going on. Just an
incredible weekend. Um, listen to this.
Saudi Crown Prince Muhammad bin Salman
called President Trump twice yesterday
urging a strike on the Houthies. Trump
refused. That was according to uh
Sentcom Commander Admiral Cooper. flew
to Riad Thursday for emergency
coordination
because the Houthies are really acting
up. And this to me is pretty major. I
mean, it could reshape the Middle East,
this region all over again once again.
It could reshape this region because it
looks like they are now the Houthies are
in control of that straight and it's
just, you know, by the Red Sea. And it
is uh incredible times we're living in.
I keep telling you guys that I don't see
um peace coming to the Middle East. I
see more war coming. And I just saw a
live studio audience member fly by in
back of the car here. So there is
somebody here. Uh this was from the Iran
observer on X. The Houthies have now
taken full control of the Red Sea and
the Babel Mandeb Strait. This
development has already had a
significant impact on the energy market.
The price of diesel in the US has
officially surpassed $6 and the price of
oil has reached $108 a barrel. In
addition, Iran has struck two oil
tankers and the Saudi oil pipeline
intended to bypass the straight of
Horamuz is likely damaged. They're not
sure about this, but they think that the
Saudi Arabian pipeline that's being
built so they wouldn't have to wouldn't
even have to like deal with the straight
of Hormuz. They think that might have
gotten blown up yesterday, part of it.
Don't know. I can't verify that yet.
This is what Amir Sarfati had to say
about this. Interesting. He said, "On
Wednesday, Saudibacked Yemeni forces
announced they had made significant
achievements on the ground in the north
and central desert areas and appeared to
have broken through Houthi lines." So,
this is the Yemen army. But in reality,
the Houthies simply repositioned their
forces, giving up the open areas so that
they could take over the more important
western coastline. By Thursday, early
morning, the Iranianbacked militia
seized the strategic coastline and port
city of Mocha. I don't know how you
pronounce that, Mocha. Mocha, MA.
Uh after government forces retreated on
mass. And so rather than an overwhelming
blitz by the Saudi backed forces, the
sides essentially swap territories with
the Houthis gaining the strategic
coastline along with the Red Sea. That's
what they wanted anyway. Looks like they
got what they wanted. This will allow
them to pose a more direct threat to
shipping in the Babel Mandeb Strait,
thus increasing the threat to Saudi
Arabia.
These things aren't just going to be
ignored, you know. These things are
we're just watching the whole Middle
East. It's on the verge of something. Do
you feel that? I mean, I know we've
watched war there since October 7th,
2023. But just it looks like something's
being framed up for something major. You
I'm hoping we're going home soon, you
know, because I really do think we're
living in the last days. I'm waiting for
Jesus. I'm not predicting a day or an
hour, but I'm saying I hope we go home
soon.
Then again, Amir said the Yemen's
Houthies seized the Pum the Mayun island
and completed the control of the Bal Bab
al-Mandde. According to reports,
uh the Houthis backed by Iran has
completed its takeover of the island of
Mayun Pam uh located at the heart of the
Babel Elmanddeb Strait. If these reports
are accurate, Amir said this move gives
the organization direct physical control
over one of the world's most sensitive
and important shipping and energy
routes.
So you got Iran playing with the
straight over and now you got the
Houthis controlling this route. And uh
you know so far the Houthies are saying
no we we'll let everything go as normal.
Everything's fine. Yeah. Okay. We'll see
how long that lasts. Uh again, Yemen's
Houthies took over key islands in the
Red Sea, completing their push to seize
the control of that straight.
What else?
The Houthies gained control of Yemen's
Red Sea, threatening the key shipping
route. And I really believe that as we
go further down this path, at some point
they are going to say, and it's going to
be to do with Israel. Oh, we're not
going to let anything come through that
has anything to do with Israel. That's
coming probably in the next few days.
Who knows? You know,
Iran's Supreme Leader's advisor says the
Houthi advance in Yemen is a resounding
victory. Of course, he'd say that, you
know.
Then we got this. Iran fires
electrooptical missile for the first
time aiming at US warships. According to
reports, Iran used its new
electrooptical missiles for the first
time in an attempted attack on US
warships on Wednesday, officials
claimed.
There you go. They got a new missile
that didn't work because it didn't hit
anything. It got fired out of the sky
from what I heard. [snorts]
And then this is so true. One more from
Air Sarati because this is so true. He
said, "The Iranians don't stop.
Construction continues at Pickax
Mountain, deep inside their newest and
most heavily fortified nuclear facility.
Their proxies in Yemen are gaining
control of a strategic coastal region
and moving closer to the Babel Elmand
Debstrate and they have it now. For the
millionth time, this regime was not made
for packs, deals, or any form of
compromise. This jihadist regime will
not stop until it fulfills what it
believes is its all-given goal, either
to dominate the world or plunge it into
the chaos necessary for the Mahi to to
appear.
Someone asked me whether the war with
Iran had ended. My answer was clear. It
hasn't even started. Anything short of
breaking the neck of this regime will
not bring peace to the region. It will
only invite the next war. And we all
know what the future holds. There will
be another war. And I think he's
speaking of the Ezekiel 38 war. And yes,
that's why they will not be completely
destroyed right now. Iran, no way, no
how.
And again, Iran continues their
ballistic missile production in
underground facilities despite US and
Israeli claims of major destruction. Uh
they're talking about Pickax Mountain,
and I'm not going to sing the song. I
told you I'm done with that song.
[laughter] I know you guys want to hear
the song, but I'm done with that song.
We got to move on. Turn the page. Okay.
Just like I guess I should address this.
Um, many people are asking about this.
Uh, at the beginning of my videos, I
always played this theme song and did it
for I don't know about a year and a
half. Um, and it was a song that Mark
and I wrote, watching River Music. And
the reason I stopped playing it is when
I was looking at my analytics of
YouTube, I realized that new viewers,
80 to 90% of them would leave within 10
seconds. That is when that song was
still playing.
And I'm trying to fish for men here. I
share the gospel every day. And I
thought it's way more important for new
viewers who are brought in by the title
of the video or the thumbnail for me to
get right to things than for them to
hear the opening theme song because then
they're leaving. And we want more people
on the ark. And many people have been
led to the Lord and believe in the
gospel because of these videos. So we're
fishing for men. So the theme the theme
song is still at the end of the video.
And you can always find it the whole
song on the Watch and River music
channel. So that's the reason I keep
forgetting to address that. It's like
the fourth or fifth day I think that I
haven't used it. So there you go. It's
still there at the end. And then we got
this. Bubba News shared this on Telegram
today ahead of Rashana cuz he wrote this
last night. Netanyahu made this pledge
directly at the Western Wall. Quote,
"President Trump announced this evening
that Iran is trying to arm itself again
with nuclear weapons. That is correct. I
pledge to you here at the Western Wall
ahead of Rashashana. As long as I am
prime minister, Iran will not have
nuclear weapons." And he ended with a
promise saying, quote, "More to come."
Bubba said, "Notice how Israel has
continued to taunt Iran this entire
week. It's as if they are playing
chicken in the street. You don't taunt
unapologetically
without knowing that you have the
knockout punch. True. Right there. True.
It's why we're seeing everything right
now is just something we're on the verge
of something huge in the Middle East. I
think most of you see that. According to
the comments, most of you do. Uh this is
from Israel today on Telegram. The
Israeli army on Thursday night destroyed
the underground facilities in the Ali
Alahir Ridge area of southern Lebanon
after recently establishing operational
control over the strategic Hezbollah
installation. The terrorist
infrastructure that was dismantled
extended for more than 2 kilometers.
Dozens of Iranian-made rockets,
missiles, and UAVs, as well as machine
guns, dozens of anti-tank missiles, and
hundreds of mines and explosive devices
were located inside. Well, if you
noticed in the video, they are no longer
there. They went kaboomi. That was a
massive explosion. They said it even
caused a 4.1 earthquake in the region.
So, there you go. And this was Netanyahu
and Defense Minister Kat's reaction.
This is what they said. This was a
strategic terror infrastructure built
over two decades with Iranian funding
and planning. The terror infrastructure
and the command center on the ridge were
designed to serve as the staging base
for the conquest of the Galilee and had
observation and fire dominance over
Matula and Karat Shimona. Their
destruction completes the achievement of
operational control over this ridge
above and below ground. So there you go.
It is no more as of right now. It's
gone.
What else
you guys? Okay,
it might be the right time. You know
what I'm going to say? You pause the
video, you go get yourself a snack.
Okay.
Uh Amir Sarati in speaking about how
this Hezbollah command center was blown
up, he said, "Will Iran respond as it
promised?" Because Iran kept saying, "If
you blow that up, we're going to
respond." They blew it up last night. Is
Iran going to respond?
What are we looking at this weekend? Who
knows?
Israel today shared this on Telegram.
American opinion turns against Israel.
Well, when you watch, watch the
mainstream media. Just watch it. You
know, they brainwashed everyone. A new
Quinnipiaak poll finds that more
registered US voters now sympathize with
the Palestinians than with the Israelis.
A dramatic shift from the overwhelming
support Israel received after Hamas's
October 7th massacre. The results
underscore the political and cultural
challenge facing Israel as the war
against Hamas and Iran's terror network
continues.
Yeah, the whole world's going to turn
against Israel. It's foretold. You know,
we get tomorrow's news today because we
have the word of God. You know, the
entire world is going to turn against
them, including the United States
completely at some point.
What else? This was from Insider Paper.
Iran and China among countries that have
used AI to aid spying. Anthropic says in
one case, Iranian actors developed a way
to identify people through their social
media accounts. Lovely. Anthropic also
disrupted efforts by users to design
weapons, conduct uh questionable
biological research, and create dating
scams. Well, there you go.
Then we got some news about Russia. NATO
confronted Russian submarines testing
secret weapon aimed at undersea cables.
Uh Reuters reported this that British,
Norwegian, and US forces tracked and
confronted Russian submarines near
Svalbard. uh disrupting an exercise
involving technology designed to disable
vital undersea cables without leaving
clear traces. Now, this report came out
yesterday, but they're talking about
this operation took place, I think, back
in April, if I'm if I'm correct. I think
it was back in April.
Then we got the big bricks pow-wow going
on this weekend. Uh Russian President
Putin arrived in New Delhi, India for
the bricks talks, the bricks summit. Uh,
China says it is ready to work with
BRICS members in long-term cooperation
and development. That is the new world
order forming right there. Iranian
president poses, he arrived in India for
the bricks summit. So, they're all
meeting, you know, you got the you got
the mayor of Iran, you got the mayor of
Russia, and you got the mayor of China.
Actually, the, you know, presidents and
but they're all meeting big pow-wow
bricks. Everyone's going to be there.
cookies, foods from many lands, all
stuff that we won't be able to take part
in. Quite frankly, I don't think I'd
want to be there. But anyway, Russia
warns, this is from Insider Paper,
Russia warns it would aim its nuclear
warheads at Lithuania if NATO allies
store nuclear weapons on Lithuanian
territory.
And this is after Lithuania plans to
lift its constitutional ban on storing
nuclear weapons to strengthen security
amid Russia's war in Ukraine. And the
Kremlin spokesperson uh Dmitri Pescov
called the plan a very serious turn and
warned it would escalate tensions and
place Lithuania in Russia's crosshairs.
Rumors of wars. Weren't we told? Didn't
Jesus tell us? I mean, this world is
just I there's one word I won't use to
describe this world right now. Stable.
It just, you know, it's just crazy what
we're seeing right now. Really crazy.
Again, the US national average diesel
price has crossed $6 a gallon for the
very first time ever. Six bucks a gallon
for diesel. Credible.
What else? Insider paper shared this.
The US weather agency said Thursday that
the El Nino pattern in the Pacific was
strengthening and there was a 75% chance
it would reach historic intensity this
year. There's only four months left to
this year. Forecasters have been
tracking an exceptional El Nino this
year as the climate phenomenon has
gained pace driving tropical Pacific sea
temperatures to record highs. Scientists
are increasingly confident that this
super El Nino, and no, it's not a
computerized vacuum cleaner. It just
sounds like one. Uh, it could exceed any
in the modern era with potentially
damaging knock-on impacts around the
globe. So, there you go. They're looking
at this Super El Nino. And no, it's not
a vacuum cleaner. Only to me, it is.
Super El Nino. Cleans your carpets in
seconds flat.
Earthquakes to last 24 hours. 47 over
4.0. 0 and 16 over 5.0. So there you go.
There was actually one that came in
about an hour before I hit record at
6.2. It was in Indonesia, but they
lowered it to a 5.9.
So there you go. You are caught up. And
one day soon, we will be caught up to
meet the King of Kings and the Lord of
Lords. Which leads me to the question of
the day. What is your favorite verse
about grace?
That's my question of the day and I'm no
longer going to answer these questions
because um I like to see your answers
and uh maybe the next day I will answer
the question uh when I read some some of
the answers. Okay, but that's your
question. What's your favorite verse
regarding grace?
All right, it is time to go to C l
world.
Okay.
Anthropic says it blocked possible
attempts to use AI to develop boweapons.
Let's get out of clown world, please.
Quickly.
It says it blocked multiple accounts
that use the company's artificial
intelligence models in ways that could
support the development of biological
weapons. In a report published yesterday
on Thursday, the AI company known for
its clawed model said it considers
biological misuse one of the most
serious risks to artificial intelligence
models. You think so?
The new report outlines five real life
case studies in which use users
circumvented controls that block users
from specific regions and engaged in
other efforts to obfiscate the purpose
of the research to evade our safeguards.
In other words, they were cracking the
code there. They were they were using
Claude. They want to make some fun toys.
You know, one day we will never have to
talk about bioweapons and war. I can't
wait. The examples include possible gain
of function research and involve both
infectious diseases such as bird flu,
venoms, and toxins.
Looking over 30 days of activity,
anthropics said it identified about 35
distinct research efforts with
potentially concerning activity.
However, it acknowledged that it could
not be certain whether the actors
intended harm or were conducting
research for legitimate scientific
purposes. Yeah, right.
Nobody means harm in this world.
Everyone's got It was all moon beams and
lollipops. These are happy bioweapons,
you know.
Not funny. Boweapons are not funny,
really.
We're living in the last days.
How's about we read a few comments of
the day, shall we? Let's see what we got
here.
Sherry,
AI warnings remind me of the past 50
years of cigarettes having warnings that
it may be hazardous to your hazardous to
your health right on the package, but no
one pays attention until they get cancer
or emphyma.
Yeah. Yeah. They keep warning us. And
that's a good analogy. They're warning
us about AI and warning us and warning
us and warning us, but they keep
building it. They keep pushing it on us.
Thank you, sister.
Yesterday's question of the day was,
"What is your favorite chapter in the
Bible that you could read over and over
again?" Doodle Toot said, "For right
now, my top chapter is Psalm 34, but
it's because I'm memorizing it, so I'm
really concentrating on that right now.
Once I get it memorized, I'll move on to
another chapter." It's awesome, sis.
Thanks for sharing that. That is a great
psalm, by the way. Great psalm. Good
song, too. you know, Psalm 34. Mid Shane
and Shane did a great song. I don't know
what it's called. I think it might be
called Psalm 34 or something.
Can't remember. Lori,
question of the day. Her answer is
Romans 8. That's the chapter I'd be left
clinging to if you ripped my Bible out
of my hands. There's so much goodness in
that chapter, but lately I've been
focused on the promise of a resurrected
creation. all presently the the old
earth is groaning for it just like we
are. Amen. Thank you, sister. Romans 8
is amazing. A lot of Bible scholars say
it's the most important chapter in the
entire Bible. You know, it's just
incredible.
Debbie,
the most hilarious thing is that when
they are watching us, talking about all
the surveillance we talked about
yesterday, when they are watching us,
the God of the universe is watching them
and knows every thought, motive, action,
and plan they have. The watchers are
being watched. Accountability will be
certain. That's a great comment, Debbie.
Thank you.
Let's do one more. I like this comment.
from Mike. Just this year alone, we have
the disclosure of all the UFOs. We've
had some major earthquakes. We've had
major volcanoes, tornadoes, mudslides,
floodings, wildfires, and now AI says
that we're all going to be dead in less
than 10 years. I would hate to think of
living in this world without Jesus. He
definitely gives us the peace that
surpasses all understanding. Even so,
come Lord Jesus. That's a great comment,
Mike. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's hard.
You're hardressed when you when you look
at everything that's going on in this
world right now simultaneously.
You're hardressed to think there's years
left. I just I just can't imagine. You
know, I'm waiting for Jesus now. And I
know many of you are now. Today, as I
always say at the end of the video,
today is a perfectly good day for the
rapture. I'm waiting now. Am I going to
say the rapture is happening today? No,
I am not. Many people are saying it is
happening today. I am saying every day,
today is a perfectly good day for the
rapture. Do you know why I say that? I
never put my faith in a date because I
never want to wake up the next day
discouraged. And you know what? I've had
people I remember last September when
everyone was excited about I believe
September 23rd and everyone was excited
and I kept saying like, you know, don't
put your faith in that date. I don't
want to squash anyone's excitement who's
excited for the return of Jesus cuz I'm
excited for it. So, I don't want to
squash that. So, I'll never criticize
anyone for putting their faith in a
date. I will just say don't put your
faith in a date because you know what?
When all said and done, for those who
think we're definitely being raptured
today or tomorrow, you know what? If
Monday comes, are we not in the last
days anymore? Is it like game over? You
know, that's I don't I don't want to
wake up Monday morning discouraged. So,
I'm always excited for the return of
Jesus day by day. But we may have to
face Monday and I don't want to be
discouraged that day. So, I will say
again today that today is a perfectly
good day for the rapture. But keep your
eyes on Jesus. It's in his perfect
timing. The most high God is going to
send Jesus in the perfect time. But the
question is, do you know Jesus? Do you
belong to him? Do you understand what
happened 2,000 years ago, which was the
greatest event in human history? God
made an appearance on earth. Jesus was
born of a virgin, conceived by the Holy
Spirit. He left a throne in heaven to
make his appearance here. And why did he
come here? It's a love story. He came
here because he loves you so much. He
knows you can't get to heaven without
him. He knows it. And he came here to
pay for our sins with his blood. Because
without the shedding of blood, there is
no remission of sin. According to
Hebrews 9:22, blood has to be shed in
order for sin to be removed, erased,
forgiven, forgotten. And Jesus came here
to do that. Do you know why? Because he
wants to spend forever and ever with
you. And he paid your way with a serious
payment, a blood payment. He went to a
bloody cross. He died a criminal's
death. And he was fully God, fully man.
He was perfect. He never sinned, not
even once. Did he deserve to go to that
cross? Absolutely not. He did it because
he loves you and he wants to spend
forever with you. But here's the catch.
You have to believe it. He wants people
who will believe in him with their free
will. He could have created robots that
would just say hallelujah forever and
ever and he wouldn't have had to go to a
cross. He could have just But you know
what? He created us and we are fallen
creatures and we with our free will, we
have to choose to believe in the atoning
blood of Jesus and in his finished work
on the cross. He wants us to God doesn't
want anyone to perish, but that all
should come to repentance. He doesn't
want anyone to go to hell. Hell wasn't
created for mankind. It was created for
Satan and his angels. But if you hear
the good news, the gospel, and you're
like, "No, I don't want that." It's the
only other, that's the flip side to the
coin. You know, it's either eternity
with Jesus or eternity separated. That's
that's what it is. So, in order to be
saved, you just have to understand
you're a sinner that needs payment for
your sins. And when you say to Jesus,
"Jesus, I admit I'm a sinner. I know I'm
a sinner. I think things that are wrong.
I've said things that are I've done
things, said things. I'm a sinner. I
need your atoning blood to wash me white
as snow." And Jesus, now I have faith in
your blood that it'll remove my sins
away from me. all of them, past,
present, and future, and it'll wash me
white as snow. And Jesus, I believe in
your finished work on the cross. You
were nailed to that cross. That's why
you came here, and you shed that
precious blood. You died. You were
buried. And you rose again the third
day. I mean, that is amazing. And you
say, Jesus, you are the one and only
savior of the world. And now I belong to
you. At that moment of belief in the
atoning blood of Jesus and in that
beautiful gospel, the death, the burial,
the resurrection of Jesus. At that
moment, you are saved. God will place
the Holy Spirit in you. You will be
ready for the rapture if it happens
soon. You will be sealed until the day
of redemption. You will be born again.
And he won't let you out of the palm of
his hand. He wants to spend forever and
ever with you. And he paid your way.
What are you going to do with that?
Do you hear that and still say, "Well, I
just don't I just don't believe." Well,
take my challenge, okay? Pick up a
Bible. You can get them anywhere.
They're B. Dollar store has them. Pick
up a Bible. Go to the book of John and
just say this prayer before you begin.
Even if you don't believe in Jesus, say,
"Jesus, I don't even believe in you, but
if you are real, reveal yourself to me."
Because anyone with an ounce of common
sense would if Jesus is real and if
Jesus is the King of Kings and the Lord
of Lords, you'd think they would say,
"Well, if you are real, let me know."
But say that prayer. And you know what?
Start reading the book of John. Maybe
nothing will happen. Maybe you'll say,
"Tom, I wasted an hour of my life." But
you know what? Maybe everything, maybe
today is that day where everything
changes for you. Maybe today is the day
that you look back on for eternity and
say, "I remember the day when I finally
got to the end of myself and realized,
I'm a sinner and I need payment for
these sins and Jesus paid for my sins."
You know, you could have new life today.
Don't put it off. Don't put it off.
You know, you do not want to face Jesus
on judgment day when your sins are still
with you and you know it and you know
you're in trouble. You know you're
kneeling before the King of Kings and
the Lord of Lords. You know you're in
the presence of God and then you're
you're sent off to eternity separated
from God. You know, I wouldn't wish my
worst enemy there. Honestly, it's why I
share the gospel every day. I know that
wide is a path to destruction. I know
that more people will hear this who
don't know the Lord and say, "Nah, I'm
okay. I'll take my chances." than people
who will say, "Oh, Jesus, my king and my
God." But I hope that some of you have
new life today. Okay? I prayed for you
because I prayed for every person who
had watched this video before I recorded
it. So, like it or not, you have been
prayed for today. And if we're not
raptured today, and I think again today,
I think it's perfectly good day for the
rapture. But if not, God willing, I will
see you guys tomorrow. I love you guys.
>> Oh, Jesus, [music]
master, [music]
creator.
You're the alpha,
Omega. [music]
You're the King of Kings.